literacycenter.net 2011-12-07

# Literacy Center Education Network - Privacy Policy

The Literacy Center Education Network sincerely values your privacy. We have created this Privacy Policy to explain how our organization handles the personal information that you provide to us on our website: LiteracyCenter.Net. 

Your use of the LiteracyCenter.Net website constitutes an acceptance of this Privacy Policy. 

**Protecting your Privacy**

The Literacy Center Education Network (LiteracyCenter.Net) collects information from our users and donors when they elect to receive notifications from our organization. All personal information is password protected and we do not share personal information with third-parties. The LiteracyCenter.Net does not send unsolicited correspondence for marketing purposes.

**Passive Collection of Information**

The LiteracyCenter.Net may collect information about your visits to our website without you actively submitting such information. Unidentifiable information may be collected using various technologies, such as cookies and Internet tags. Your Internet browser automatically transmits to our Logs some of this unidentifiable information, such as the URL of the website you just visited and the browser version your computer is operating. Passive information collection technologies can make your use of our website easier by allowing the LiteracyCenter.Net to provide better service, customize our site based on consumer preferences, compile statistics, analyze trends, and otherwise administer and improve usability. Information collected by these technologies cannot be used to identity you without additional identifiable information. 

**Online Donations**

The LiteracyCenter.Net uses [PayPal](https://www.paypal.com/us/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/ua/policy_privacy-outside) and the [Google Shopping Cart](https://checkout.google.com/files/privacy.html) to accept online donations. Please refer to the privacy policies of these organizations to see how they handle personal information related to your donation.

**Disclosure of Information**

The LiteracyCenter.Net may disclose information about its users if required to do so by law enforcement or other governmental officials, in response to a verified request relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity; or if we believe that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or any other legal process.   
The LiteracyCenter.Net may also disclose information about its users to law enforcement officers, if there is evidence that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to claims that any content violates the rights of third-parties.

  **Securing Data**

The LiteracyCenter.Net works very hard to secure your data. All data is stored on a server located in the United States, using tools such as password protection, and physical security, to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. However, third-parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, and other users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect during these unlawful interceptions. For this reason, we can not promise that your personal information or private communications will always remain private. 

**Changes and Amendments to this Privacy Policy**

Literacy Center Education Network reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy without prior notice to reflect technological advancements, legal and regulatory changes and good business practices. If the LiteracyCenter.Net changes its privacy practices, a new Privacy Policy will reflect those changes and the effective date of the revised Privacy Policy will be set forth in this paragraph. This Privacy Policy was last updated on April 11, 2009 and is effective as of that date.

**Contacting the Literacy Center Education Network**

If you have any questions about the use, amendment, or deletion of personal information that you have provided to us, please contact us at [privacy@literacycenter.net](mailto:privacy@literacycenter.net).  You may also contact us at:

Literacy Center Education Network  
131 Vista Robles  
Ben Lomond, California 95005
